
  as3-commons
  ActionScript 3.0 Libraries  
  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------

  Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
  contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file distributed with
  this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
  The ASF licenses this file to You under the Apache License, Version 2.0
  (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with
  the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at

  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
  
  
  ADOBE SYSTEMS INCORPORATED
  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------

  Copyright 2003-2007 Adobe Systems Incorporated
  All Rights Reserved.

  NOTICE: Adobe permits you to use, modify, and distribute this file
  in accordance with the terms of the license agreement accompanying it.


  flex-iframe
  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Copyright (c) 2007-2011 flex-iframe contributors

  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
  of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
  in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
  to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
  copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
  furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
  all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
  IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
  FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
  AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
  LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
  OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
  THE SOFTWARE.
  
  
  ObjectHandles
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Copyright (c) 2010 Marc Hughes 
  
  Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a 
  copy of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), 
  to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation 
  the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, 
  and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software 
  is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
  
  The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all 
  copies or substantial portions of the Software.
  
  THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, 
  INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A 
  PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT 
  HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION 
  OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE 
  SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE. 
  
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  
  Contributions by:
  
  Alexander Kludt
  Thomas Jakobi
  Mario Ernst
  Aaron Winkler
  Gregory Tappero
  Andrew Westberg
  
  

  Multipart URL Loader
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  @author Eugene Zatepyakin
  @version 1.3
  @link http://blog.inspirit.ru/



  Base64
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
 * Copyright (C) 2012 Jean-Philippe Auclair
 * Licensed under the MIT license: http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php
 * Base64 library for ActionScript 3.0.
 * By: Jean-Philippe Auclair : http://jpauclair.net
 * Based on article: http://jpauclair.net/2010/01/09/base64-optimized-as3-lib/
 
 
 
  Ace Editor
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  The Ace source code is released under the BSD License. This license is very simple, 
  and is friendly to all kinds of projects, whether open source or not. Take charge 
  of your editor and add your favorite language highlighting and keybindings!
   
  Copyright (c) 2010, Ajax.org B.V.
  All rights reserved.
  
  Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
  modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
      * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
        notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
      * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
        notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
        documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
      * Neither the name of Ajax.org B.V. nor the
        names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
        derived from this software without specific prior written permission.
  
  THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND
  ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED
  WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE
  DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL AJAX.ORG B.V. BE LIABLE FOR ANY
  DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
  (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
  LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
  ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
  (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
  SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
  
  
  
  FTP Client
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Copyright (c) 2010, malibooo@maliboo.pl,malibooo@gmail.com
  All rights reserved.

  Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, 
  are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

  1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list 
  of conditions and the following disclaimer.

  2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list 
  of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials 
  provided with the distribution.

  3. Neither the name of the copyright holder nor the names of its contributors may be used 
  to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written 
  permission.

  THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY 
  EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF 
  MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL
  THE COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, 
  SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT 
  OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) 
  HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR 
  TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS 
  SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
  
  
  
  Jacob Schatz
  -----------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
  contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file distributed with
  this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
  The ASF licenses this file to You under the Apache License, Version 2.0
  (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with
  the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at

  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
  
  
  
  PSDParser  
  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Copyright (c) 2010 Slavomir Durej

  Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
  contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file distributed with
  this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
  The ASF licenses this file to You under the Apache License, Version 2.0
  (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance with
  the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at

  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  limitations under the License.
  
  
  
  SVG2FXG XSL
  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------
  Nicolas Dufour <nicoduf@yahoo.fr>
  
  Modifications (c) 2014 Sascha Ahrend <mail@ahrend.tel>
  
  Copyright (c) 2010 authors
  
  SVG2FXG is licensed under the terms of the General Public License (GPL)
  Version 2 or later, or alternatively under the terms of the Apache
  License Version 2.0.
  
  You may use SVG2FXG according to either of these licenses as is most
  appropriate for your project on a case-by-case basis.
  
  The terms of each license can be found in the main directory of the
  project source repository:
  
  GPL2 License: https://gitlab.com/jazzynico/svg2fxg/blob/master/LICENSE-GPL2.txt
  Apache License: https://gitlab.com/jazzynico/svg2fxg/blob/master/LICENSE-APACHE2.txt


  Additional credits have yet to be added... 